Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-2004
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Registration, 1995 March; cuid3207 (Box I:16, Folder 40)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Exhibition, 1995 March; cuid3208 (Box I:16, Folder 41)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Public Relations, 1995 April-May; cuid3209 (Box I:16, Folder 42)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Registration, 1995 March; cuid3210 (Box I:16, Folder 43)
  - Ed McGowan (Windows), 1995; cuid3211 (Box I:16, Folder 44)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis), 1992-1995; cuid3212 (Box I:16, Folder 45)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Project Rembrandt, 1995; cuid3213 (Box I:16, Folder 46)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Biographies, 1981-1995; cuid3214 (Box I:17, Folder 1)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Entry Forms, Circa 1993-1995; cuid3215 (Box I:17, Folder 2)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Registration, 1995; cuid3216 (Box I:17, Folder 3)
  - Mark Beard (Windows), 1995-1996; cuid3217 (Box I:17, Folder 4)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Background Articles, Reviews, etc., 1992 March-Circa 1996; cuid3218 (Box I:17, Folder 5)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Catalogue Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1996; cuid3219 (Box I:17, Folder 6)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Catalogue Miscellaneous (2 of 2), Circa 1995-1997; cuid3220 (Box I:17, Folder 7)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Correspondence, 1995 September-1997 August; cuid3221 (Box I:17, Folder 8)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Development, 1995-1996; cuid3222 (Box I:17, Folder 9)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Exhibition Design, Circa 1994-1997; cuid3223 (Box I:17, Folder 10)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Exhibition List, 1995-1996; cuid3224 (Box I:17, Folder 11)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Installation, 1996-1997; cuid3225 (Box I:17, Folder 12)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1994-1996; cuid3226 (Box I:17, Folder 13)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1996; cuid3227 (Box I:17, Folder 14)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Press, 1996-1997; cuid3228 (Box I:17, Folder 15)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Registration, 1995 May-1997 January; cuid3229 (Box I:17, Folder 16)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Resumes, Undated; cuid3230 (Box I:17, Folder 17)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award, 1995 August-1996 April; cuid3231 (Box I:17, Folder 18)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (1 of 3), 1996 February-July; cuid3232 (Box I:17, Folder 19)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (2 of 3), Circa 1996; cuid3233 (Box I:17, Folder 20)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (3 of 3), 1996; cuid3234 (Box I:17, Folder 21)
  - Artists from Japan -- Artists Shown, 1996; cuid3235 (Box I:17, Folder 22)
  - Artists from Japan -- Condition Reports, 1996-1997; cuid3236 (Box I:17, Folder 23)
  - Artists from Japan -- Exhibition Signage, 1996; cuid3237 (Box I:17, Folder 24)
  - Artists from Japan -- Postponement, 1996; cuid3238 (Box I:17, Folder 25)
  - Artists from Japan -- Review, 1997 February 1; cuid3239 (Box I:17, Folder 26)
  - Artists from Japan -- Shipment and Installation, 1996 June-1997 February; cuid3240 (Box I:17, Folder 27)
  - Artists from Japan -- Shipment and Installation (Documents), 1996-1997; cuid3241 (Box I:17, Folder 28)
  - Walter Gaudnek Exhibit, 1994-1996; cuid3242 (Box I:20, Folder 34)
  - The Art of the Everyday: France in the '90s, 1993-1997; cuid3243 (Box I:21, Folder 1-54, Box I:22, Folder 1-52, Cassette 1, Box I:23, Folder 9-12, Box I:30, Folder 37-46, Box I:32, Folder 1-7)
  - The First Steps: Emerging Artists from Japan, 1997-2001; cuid3244 (Box I:22, Folder 53-56, Box I:23, Folder 1-8, Box I:26, Folder 1-21, Box I:30, Folder 25-34, Box I:31, Folder 46-52, Box I:32, Folder 11-24)
    Separated Materials
    Folder 27 removed from Box I:30 to Box 31 (OS flat box). Folder contains dDk magazine, photographs, and articles. Folder labeled "The First Steps: Emerging Artists from Japan"
  - Langlands & Bell, 1991-1997; cuid3245 (Box I:23, Folder 13-28, Box I:30, Folder 35-36)
  - Nahum Zenil: Witness to the Self, 1997; cuid3246 (Box I:23, Folder 29-44)
  - Deep Storage: Arsenale der Erinnerung, 1997; cuid3247 (Box I:23, Folder 45-46)
  - War of Extermination: Wehrmacht Crimes between 1941-1944, 1997-1998; cuid3248 (Box I:23, Folder 47-55)
  - Desert Cliché: Israel Now - Local Images, 1996-1998; cuid3249 (Box I:23, Folder 56-67, Box I:24, Folder 1-4)
  - Shiro Kuramata: 1934-1991, 1997-1998; cuid3250 (Box I:24, Folder 5-60)
  - Police Pictures: The Photograph as Evidence, 1997-1998; cuid3251 (Box I:24, Folder 61-69, Box I:25, Folder 1-18)
  - Maya Lin: Topologies, 1996-1998; cuid3252 (Box I:25, Folder 19-44)
  - Counter Culture: Parisian Cabarets and the Avant-Garde, 1875-1905, 1996-1999; cuid3253 (Box I:25, Folder 45-70)
  - When Time Began to Rant and Rage: Figurative Painting from Twentieth-Century Ireland, 1998-2000; cuid3254 (Box I:26, Folder 22-61)
  - John Singer Sargent, Draughtsman: Works from the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1999; cuid3255 (Box I:26, Folder 62-72)
  - Inverted Odysseys: Claude Cahun, Maya Deren, Cindy Sherman, 1998-2000; cuid3256 (Box I:27, Folder 1-92, Box I:28, Folder 1-11, Box I:30, Folder 1-6)
  - Sheer Realities: Clothing and Power in Nineteenth-Century Philippines, 1999-2000; cuid3257 (Box I:28, Folder 12-25)
  - Rudy Burckhardt and Friends: New York Artists of the 1950s and '60s, 2000-2003; cuid3258 (Box I:28, Folder 26-50, Box I:29, Folder 1-19)
  - Face to Face: Shiseido and the Manufacture of Beauty, 1900-2000, 1999-2000; cuid3259 (Box I:29, Folder 20-51, Box I:31, Folder 1-26)
    Folder 46 removed from Box I:29 to Box 31 (OS flat box). New folders labeled "Shiseido: Checklist of Art (1)" and "Shiseido: Checklist of Art (2)"
    Folder 12 removed from Box I:31 to Box 31 (OS flat box). New folder labeled "Exhibition Objects, Shiseido Collection--Database Report (2)"
  - Krizia: A Story, 1998-1999; cuid3260 (Box I:30, Folder 7-24)
  - Ben Shahn's New York: The Photography of Modern Times, 1999-2001; cuid3261 (Box I:31, Folder 27-45, Box I:32, Folder 8-10)
  - Dreams and Disillusion: Karel Teige and the Czech Avant-Garde, 2000-2001; cuid3262 (Box I:31, Folder 53-66, Box I:32, Folder 25-26)
  - Shifting Tides: Cuban Photography after the Revolution, 2000-2001; cuid3263 (Box I:32, Folder 27-28, Box I:33, Folder 1-17)
  - The Park Avenue Cubists: Gallatin, Morris, Frelinghuysen, and Shaw, 2000-2004; cuid3264 (Box I:32, Folder 29-44, Box I:35, Folder 42-79, Box I:36, Folder 1)
  - Pastoral to Post-Industrial: British Works on Paper from the Whitworth Art Gallery, 2001-2002; cuid3265 (Box I:33, Folder 18-37)
  - Seeing and Believing: The Art of Nancy Burson, 2000-2003; cuid3266 (Box I:33, Folder 38-61, Box I:34, Folder 1-11)
  - Priceless Children: American Photographs 1890-1925/ Child Labor and the Pictorialist Ideal, 2001-2002; cuid3267 (Box I:34, Folder 12-20)
  - Between Word and Image: Modern Iranian Visual Culture, 2001-2003; cuid3268 (Box I:34, Folder 21-60, Box I:35, Folder 1-41)
  - Park Avenue Cubists, 2001-2003; cuid3269 (Box 32)
  - Swiss Peaks, 2001-2003; cuid3270 (Box 32)
  - Swiss Peaks, 2001-2003; cuid3271 (Box 33)
  - Paul Kos, 2001-2003; cuid3272 (Box 33)
  - Diane Arbus, 2001-2004; cuid3273 (Box 33)
  - Erró, 2001-2004; cuid3274 (Box 33)
    Folder removed from Box 33 to Box 31 (OS flat box). Folder contains portraits of artists. New folder labeled "Photos de Film (Grimace) 1962-1967 D' Gudmundur Erro"
  - Erró, 2001-2004; cuid3275 (Box 34)
  - Atsuko Tanaka, 2001-2004; cuid3276 (Box 34)
  - Atsuko Tanaka, 2001-2004; cuid3277 (Box 35)
  - Mapping/Sitting, 2002-2005; cuid3278 (Box 35)
  - Ok/Okay, 2002-2005; cuid3279 (Box 36)
  - Paper Museums, 2002-2005; cuid3280 (Box 36)
  - The Downtown Show, 2003-2006; cuid3281 (Box 36)
  - The Downtown Show, 2003-2006; cuid3282 (Box 37)
  - Moving Pictures, 2004-2006; cuid3283 (Box 37)
  - Moving Pictures, 2004-2006; cuid3284 (Box 38)
  - Lee Mullican, 2004-2006; cuid3285 (Box 38)
  - The Downtown Show, 2004-2006; cuid3286 (Box 38)
  - The Downtown Show, 2004-2006; cuid3287 (Box 39)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1997-2007; cuid3288 (Box 30)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1997-2007; cuid3289 (Box 40)
  - Americans in Paris: Artists Working in Postwar France, 1946-1962 Exhibition Catalog, 2022 (Box 51)
  - OS Removals (Box 31)
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988
  This series contains administrative and development files, correspondence, WNYC recordings, and annual reports of New York University Art Collection and the Grey Art Gallery.
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1959-1977
    This subseries consists of letters of acknowledgement and other communications regarding donations to the New York University Art Collection and the Grey Art Gallery.
    - Chronological Miscellaneous Coorespondence, 1959-1969 (Box II:1, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Faculty Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box II:1, Folder 2)
    - Chronological File -- February-July 1967, 1967 February-July (Box II:1, Folder 3)
    - Chronological File -- August-December 1967, 1967 August-December (Box II:1, Folder 4)
    - Chronological File -- January-June 1968, 1968 January-June (Box II:1, Folder 5)
    - Chronological File -- July-December 1968, 1968 July-December (Box II:1, Folder 6)
    - Chronological File -- 1969 (Box II:1, Folder 7)
    - Chronological File -- 1970 (Box II:1, Folder 8)
    - Chronological File -- 1971 (Box II:1, Folder 9)
    - Chronological File -- 1972 (Box II:1, Folder 10)
    - Chronological File -- 1973 (1 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 11)
    - Chronological File -- 1973 (2 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 12)
    - Chronological File -- 1974 (Box II:1, Folder 13)
    - Chronological File -- 1975 (1 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 14)
    - Chronological File -- 1975 (2 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 15)
    - Chronological File - JAS (1 of 2), 1976 (Box II:1, Folder 16)
    - Chronological File - JAS (2 of 2), 1976 (Box II:1, Folder 17)
    - Chronological File - JAS, 1976-1977 (Box II:1, Folder 18)
    - Thank You Letters -- 1967-1969 (Box II:1, Folder 19)
    - Thank You Letters -- 1969-1971 (Box II:1, Folder 20)
  - Subseries B: Grey, 1973-1980
    This subseries contains correspondence, memoranda, notes, newspaper clippings, printed materials and other miscellaneous materials relating to the foundation of the Grey Art Gallery and its involvement with Abby Grey.
    - Donor, 1973-1975 (Box II:1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1980 May (Box II:1, Folder 22)
    - Honorary Dinner, 1979-1980 (Box II:1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence for Mrs. Abby, 1975-1979 (Box II:1, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: WNYC, 1968-1973
    This subseries contains audiovisual recordings of Ruth Bowman, the curator of the New York University Art Collection, related to her involvement in a television and radio series titled, "Views on Art." The subseries also includes correspondence, drafts, notes and printed materials.
    - Radio - "View on Art", 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 25)
    - Radio - "View on Art", 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 26)
    - TV - One to One (1 of 2), 1968-1972 (Box II:1, Folder 27)
    - TV - One to One (2 of 2), 1968-1972 (Box II:1, Folder 28)
    - TV, 1969-1970 (Box II:1, Folder 29)
    - TV, 1970-1971 (Box II:1, Folder 30)
    - TV, 1971-1972 (Box II:1, Folder 31)
    - TV (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 32)
    - TV (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-1980
    This subseries consists of applications, rejections and acceptances for the NEH, NEA and NYSCA grants; loan agreements, rejected loans, lender information and correspondence; insurance certificates, shipping, delivery and transportation receipts and paperwork; condition reports, appeals for funds, funding sources and resumes.
    - AFA Ancient Mexico Exhibit, 1964 November 3 (Box II:2, Folder 1)
    - Loan Return Forms -- New York Painter, 1967 (Box II:2, Folder 2)
    - Lenders, 1967 April-October (Box II:2, Folder 3)
    - New York State Council on the Arts - Grant Application, 1970 June-August (Box II:2, Folder 4)
    - 1971 Grant Application -- NYSCA (Box II:2, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions: University of Connecticut, 1972 October 2 (Box II:2, Folder 6)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1972 (Box II:2, Folder 7)
    - Helena Rubenstein Foundation Grant, 1973-1974 (Box II:2, Folder 8)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1973-1975 (Box II:2, Folder 9)
    - Exhibitions Print Show - Hudson River Museum, 1973 January 13-March 4 (Box II:2, Folder 10)
    - Alan Sonfist - Rejected Exhibition Proposal, 1973 December-1975 December (Box II:2, Folder 11)
    - Grant Proposals, 1974 (Box II:2, Folder 12)
    - NEH Grants Rejected -- Ashcan Painters, 1974 (Box II:2, Folder 13)
    - Draft Proposal -- NYSCA General Operations, 1974-1975 (Box II:2, Folder 14)
    - NEA Grant -- Prints and Techniques, 1975-1976 (Box II:2, Folder 15)
    - Prints and Technique Working File, 1976 March-April (Box II:2, Folder 16)
    - NYSCA 2nd Proposal - Joy Gordon, 1975-1976 (Box II:2, Folder 17)
    - Loans -- Sara Roby Exhibition, 1976 January-March (Box II:2, Folder 18)
    - Udine Receipts, 1976 July-August (Box II:2, Folder 19)
    - NYSCA Program Proposal (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box II:2, Folder 20)
    - NYSCA Program Proposal (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box II:2, Folder 21)
    - Circa 1776 NEA Grant, 1976-1977 (Box II:2, Folder 22)
    - Circa 1776 Loans, 1976 June-October (Box II:2, Folder 23)
    - 1776 Exhibition Loans, 1976 June-November (Box II:2, Folder 24)
    - NYSCA Grant Preparatory Notes, circa 1976-1978 (Box II:2, Folder 25)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum Show, 1976 June-December (Box II:2, Folder 26)
    - Tanavolil Shipping and Insurance, 1976 August-1977 January (Box II:2, Folder 27)
    - Parviz Tanavoli Exhibition Billing, 1976 November 10-23 (Box II:2, Folder 28)
    - Beatrix Potter -- American Lenders Correspondence (1 of 2), 1976 November-1977 July (Box II:2, Folder 29)
    - Beatrix Potter -- American Lenders Correspondence (2 of 2), 1976 November-1977 July (Box II:2, Folder 30)
    - Beatrix Potter Correspondence to Armitt Trust, 1976 November-1978 January (Box II:2, Folder 31)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (1 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November (Box II:2, Folder 32)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (2 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November (Box II:2, Folder 33)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (3 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November (Box II:2, Folder 34)
    - Information on Lenders [Beatrix Potter] (1 of 2), 1977 February-May (Box II:2, Folder 35)
    - Information on Lenders [Beatrix Potter] (2 of 2), 1977 February-May (Box II:2, Folder 36)
    - Beatrix Potter Toronto-Boston Loans, 1977 April-June (Box II:2, Folder 37)
    - Grants Pending/Accepted -- NEH Futurist Exhibition (1 of 2), 1977 (Box II:2, Folder 38)
    - Grants Pending/Accepted -- NEH Futurist Exhibition (2 of 2), 1977 (Box II:2, Folder 39)
    - Ree Morton Loans, 1977 May-August (Box II:2, Folder 40)
    - Drawing and Collage Loans, 1977 May-October (Box II:2, Folder 41)
    - Philadelphia Museum Correspondence - Gallery of Living Art Revisited, 1977-1978 (Box II:2, Folder 42)
    - Berkshire Museum Correspondence - "Gallery of Living Art", 1977-1978 (Box II:2, Folder 43)
    - Panoramic Photography, 1977-1979 (Box II:2, Folder 44)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders A-K, 1977 May-1978 January (Box II:2, Folder 45)
    - History of Panoramic Photo - Insurance, 1977 May-September (Box II:2, Folder 46)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders L, 1977 June-December (Box II:2, Folder 47)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1977 June-December (Box II:3, Folder 1)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1977 June-December (Box II:3, Folder 2)
    - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman Loan Forms and Memos, 1977 January-1978 December 29 (Box II:3, Folder 3)
    - Wilmarth/Sandman Exhibition (Insurance and Transportation), 1977 November-1978 July (Box II:3, Folder 4)
    - Wilmarth Black/White Photos, 1978 September-October (Box II:3, Folder 5)
    - The Jewish Way of Death - NEH (Pending) (Rejected), 1978 (Box II:3, Folder 6)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Works in NY Show Only (1 of 2), 1978 May-December (Box II:3, Folder 7)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Works in NY Show Only (2 of 2), 1978 May-December (Box II:3, Folder 8)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Registrar's Files Miscellaneous, 1978 September-1979 January (Box II:3, Folder 9)
    - Gallatin -- Lenders, 1978-1979 (Box II:3, Folder 10)
    - On the Square -- NEH Planning, 1978-1979 (Box II:3, Folder 11)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders A-L (1 of 2), 1978 March-1979 June (Box II:3, Folder 12)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders A-L (2 of 2), 1978 March-1979 December (Box II:3, Folder 13)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1978 March-1979 June (Box II:3, Folder 14)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1978 March-1979 June (Box II:3, Folder 15)
    - Tiffany -- Auxiliary Loans, 1979 March-May (Box II:3, Folder 16)
    - Russian Show -- NEH (Revised), 1979 (Box II:3, Folder 17)
    - Looking at Art -- NEA Grant, 1979 (Box II:3, Folder 18)
    - Life -- Blank Contracts, 1979 November 5 (Box II:13, Folder 18)
    - Life -- Blank Facilities Reports, Undated (Box II:13, Folder 19)
    - Life -- Bookings (No Response or Rejections), 1977 November-1979 October (Box II:13, Folder 20)
    - Life -- Bookings Pending, 1979 May-1980 December (Box II:13, Folder 21)
    - Life -- Budget, 1979 May-August (Box II:13, Folder 22)
    - Life -- Catalog Orders, 1979 June-September (Box II:13, Folder 23)
    - Life -- Time, Inc. Correspondence, 1978 August-1979 April (Box II:13, Folder 24)
    - Life -- Correspondence, 1979 May-August (Box II:13, Folder 25)
    - Life -- Crate List, Circa 1979-1980 (Box II:13, Folder 26)
    - Life -- Frames and Crates (Costs), 1979 March (Box II:13, Folder 27)
    - Life -- Insurance List, Circa 1979-1980 (Box II:13, Folder 28)
    - Life -- NEA, 1978-1979 (Box II:13, Folder 29)
    - Life -- NEA Application Resubmission, 1979-1980 (Box II:13, Folder 30)
    - Life -- Opening and Catalog, 1979 May-October (Box II:13, Folder 31)
    - Life -- PR Memos and Correspondence, 1979 March-July (Box II:13, Folder 32)
    - Life -- Press Photos Sent, 1979 March-July (Box II:13, Folder 33)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Claremont College, March 10-Apr. 13, 1980), 1979 July-1980 September (Box II:13, Folder 34)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Claremont College, March 10-Apr. 13, 1980), 1979 July (Box II:13, Folder 35)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Dartmouth Museum, Sept. 14-Nov. 2), 1979 June-July (Box II:13, Folder 36)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Dartmouth Museum, Sept. 14-Nov. 2), 1979 July (Box II:13, Folder 37)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Delaware Art Museum, OCt. 15-Dec. 2, 1979), 1979 May-December (Box II:13, Folder 38)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Doris O'Neil Correspondence), 1978 November-1980 December (Box II:13, Folder 39)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Exeter Academy, May 15-June 15, 1981), 1981 March-July (Box II:13, Folder 40)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Exeter Academy, May 15-June 15, 1981), 1979 July (Box II:13, Folder 41)
    - Life -- Traveling Show Fact Sheets, Circa 1979-1981 (Box II:13, Folder 42)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Keene State College, Aug. 31-Sept. 28, 1980), 1979-1981 (Box II:13, Folder 43)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Keene State College, Aug. 31-Sept. 28, 1980), 1979-1981 (Box II:13, Folder 44)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Lufkin Historical, Texas), 1979 July-November (Box II:13, Folder 45)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Lufkin Historical, Texas), 1979 July-August (Box II:13, Folder 46)
    - Lilfe -- Traveling Show (Minnesota May-June 22, 1980), 1979 October-1980 October (Box II:13, Folder 47)
    - Lilfe -- Traveling Show (Minnesota May-June 22, 1980), 1979 December-1980 July (Box II:13, Folder 48)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Notre Dame, Oct. - Nov., 1981), 1980 Janaury-February (Box II:13, Folder 49)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Notre Dame, Oct.-Nov., 1981), 1980 February-March (Box II:13, Folder 50)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (St. Louis, March-May 2, 1981), 1979 November-1981 April (Box II:13, Folder 51)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (St. Louis, March-May 2, 1981), 1979 November (Box II:13, Folder 52)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Transportation), 1979 March-December (Box II:13, Folder 53)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Valparaiso University, Jan. 15-Feb. 25, 1980), 1978-1980 March (Box II:13, Folder 54)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Vancouver, July-Aug. 24, 1980), 1979 September-1980 October (Box II:13, Folder 55)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Vancouver, July-Aug. 24, 1980), 1979 November (Box II:13, Folder 56)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (University of Pittsburgh, Jan. 1-Feb 28, 1981), 1979 August-1981 March (Box II:13, Folder 57)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (University of Pittsburgh, Jan. 1-Feb 28, 1981), 1979 September-1981 March (Box II:13, Folder 58)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Wheelabrator Frye), 1979 May-1980 July (Box II:13, Folder 59)
    - American Painting -- Barbara Rose Catalogue Sales, 1979 September-December (Box II:13, Folder 60)
    - American Painting -- Gary Reynold's File, 1979 June-October (Box II:13, Folder 61)
    - American Painting -- New York Council on the Humanities, 1979 June-August (Box II:13, Folder 62)
    - American Painting -- Photographs Sent Out, 1979 September-1980 March (Box II:13, Folder 63)
    - American Painting -- SCM Corporation, 1979 June-September (Box II:13, Folder 64)
    - American Painting -- Symposium, 1979 July-October (Box II:13, Folder 65)
    - American Symbolist -- Budget, 1976 December-1979 June (Box II:13, Folder 66)
    - American Symbolist -- Funding, 1977 December-1979 October (Box II:13, Folder 67)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Rejections, 1978 Janaury-1979 April (Box II:13, Folder 68)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Rejects, 1979 April-October (Box II:13, Folder 69)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Requests (1 of 2), 1977 December-1978 March (Box II:13, Folder 70)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Requests (2 of 2), 1977 December-1978 February (Box II:13, Folder 71)
    - American Symbolist -- Loans (1 of 2), 1977 December-1978 February (Box II:13, Folder 72)
    - American Symbolist -- Loans (2 of 2), 1977 December-1978 February (Box II:13, Folder 73)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders A-L (1 of 2), 1979 April-1980 June (Box II:13, Folder 74)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders A-L (2 of 2), 1979 April-October (Box II:13, Folder 75)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1979 March-1980 January (Box II:13, Folder 76)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1979 April-1980 January (Box II:13, Folder 77)
    - American Symbolist -- Insurance, 1979 August-1980 February (Box II:14, Folder 1)
    - American Symbolist -- Insurance, 1979 September-October (Box II:14, Folder 2)
    - American Symbolist -- Shipping Arrangements, 1979 September-December (Box II:14, Folder 3)
    - American Symbolist -- Travel and Financial, 1977 December-1978 November (Box II:14, Folder 4)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Auxiliary Fund, 1979 July-1980 April (Box II:14, Folder 5)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Funding, 1976 December-1980 March (Box II:14, Folder 6)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Invitations, 1978 December-1979 December (Box II:14, Folder 7)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Auxillary Loans, 1979 November-1980 September (Box II:14, Folder 8)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Boston Loan, 1977 October-1980 January (Box II:14, Folder 9)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Licht Collection Loan, 1979 October-1980 June (Box II:14, Folder 10)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Musee Cantonal Loans, 1978 March-1980 January (Box II:14, Folder 11)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Musee Cantonal Loans, 1979 February-December (Box II:14, Folder 12)